<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Catalog</string>

    <string name="json">https://manucure-3e06f.firebaseio.com/manicure.json</string>
    <string name="neednetwork">Требуется подключение к Интернету</string>

    <string name="Idei">Идеи</string>
    <string name="idedi1000">Тысячи идей для вас</string>

    <string name="stati">Статьи</string>
    <string name="interesnoe">Интересное рядом</string>

    <string name="faorite">Избранное</string>
    <string name="favoritetext">Добавьте, что понравится</string>

    <string name="ourapps">Наши приложения</string>
    <string name="youlikeit">Найтиде что-то новое для себя</string>

    <string name="aboutapp">О приложении</string>
    <string name="moreaboutapp">Подробнее</string>




    <string name="offer1title">Offer 1 Title</string>
    <string name="offer1text">Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 TextOffer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 TextOffer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 TextOffer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text.Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 TextOffer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 TextOffer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 TextOffer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. Offer 1 Text. </string>

    <string name="offer2title">Offer 2 Title</string>
    <string name="offer2text">Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. Offer 2 Text. </string>

    <string name="offer3title">Offer 3 Title</string>
    <string name="offer3text">Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. Offer 3 Text. </string>
</resources>
